what obscure piece
all right so you guys saw yesterday I
reviewed a 20-17
Oda for so this is my dad this is my mom
and this is this is me on my dad is a
one of the many shipper plus users we
have out there by the way I didn't
realize that FCW works in ship for plus
Samba dads use that is the audio with
shipper plus the shipper plus it's not
self driving so this is I think it's a
is it a midnight black I don't think
it's a midnight black I think if there's
128 gig iam right guy thinks I'm 28 kg
out I gave it to my dad for Christmas
should I get an accident so if I give
you no no I mean the real tragedy is
guys if this is part of the review of
the car I've been trying to pair my
phone to this stereo system how long
that's my security put in that
got about 10 minutes something that's
okay I don't think was ten minutes like
that's a little bit exaggerating but but
oh oh I didn't really look at systems
over there
I mean your car had a screen over there
I drove this car to the bagel shop this
morning now you know my dad keeps it
impeccably clean oh yeah this is running
chef replies we have an updated chef
reply yet we'll push that update when I
get back
here's EZ Pass that could easily be
incorporated with wait Haley
but yeah break easy that's it we should
be able to do that no I don't believe it
has lks or ACC have digital up does this
have electric or hydraulic power
steering I don't know it feels it feels
hydraulic any paint oxidation
mom you have a name stethoscope he's I
love my son cute
yay , buy the merchandise bro oh we
shall I've been showing him a jig Paul's
music that's what I was trying to play
on the Bluetooth audio but no luck you
know well some a fan of guys Danielle
we're Goldie check out high bish remix
her last verse on their fire buy them
their fans alright guys so this is yeah
I don't think this car is self-driving
[Music]
my parents also have a 2006 x3 BMW yeah
time where we're on our way to a wedding
we're no way to a wedding my dress nice
yeah we shout no we shouting that out
just get me gift
oh I gotta go so I got a gift alright yo
you guys come hoodies our house knocking
get them a compatible car that's what
they want it's wedding time give them a
neon
that's a good idea
did she now is it does have a Touring
package to work well if it's doing is
that car that's a Bosch radar isn't it
isn't it or me
Bosch Reiter I was time to support them
yeah I was telling I was telling my mom
rav4 hybrid yeah yeah is that what is
that would you like no way what did it
know what you like the best
I mean what do you want is a replacement
for the BMW well those have guys well I
can't why don't let's let's ask I'm
gonna switch you guys to the front
why don't we support BMW
the German for the chairman that's okay
it's not the German assets' the problem
up the bounty we could up the bounty
flex ray yeah oh that's right yeah so
yeah my dad my dad's got a panda down
here
panda um no they would suck I don't know
I like BMW sir right beaten his dad says
BMWs break is that true mom my mom did
get rear-ended on the highway though not
not that fast it's all right but uh BMWs
BMWs break that's what that's what a
scope he was saying tell you about flex
rent so flex raise 10 megabit um so
unlike can it's a scheduled protocol
which means there's like Windows and
schedules the messages it is more
real-time but it's annoying it was only
like expensive chips and stuff supported
um it was a dying standard I'm shocked
at its in as many cars as it's in I'm
surprised they don't move to Ethernet
you've got to move to eat than that
death mono class use Ethernet all right
they should you think that's a good
choice
there's nobody that does believe I know
anything it what season it bloody the
debunked Ethernet Ethernet was named
after or the the intoxicant either what
are my parents do for a living you guys
want to talk about that I run the
networks at a girls Catholic High School
I don't like that wise mom I don't like
that was that's right that's right
just work is life grows right Marcus
that's true thank you
you know what happens yeah good good
does you know what happens to people who
don't work their minds start to
deteriorate you gotta work know your
mind is fine mom you just gotta work
work good job building the wall I had to
be more politically correct in my
periscope okay we got to be politically
correct um we support everybody's right
to a long wait is that
a job yes some global warming did Cruz
hacks microwave for their first Audi
cars I don't think so I think those
Audi's didn't have flexpay I actually
think the a4 last generation whoa mom
de-escalating deescalate to escalate
conflict good strategy don't be excited
by the shop , da di gray pandas are
coming back in stock as soon as I fly
back to California
I feel so professional doing this in a
suit but yeah don't buy a 2013 Nissan
Altima I think that's the conclusion
with us they've cleaned it up first
I did I did really enjoy renting that
Audi yesterday I rented it with silver
cars shoutout to silver car they didn't
give me a discount
nobody ever gives me any discount just
show for him anyway why aren't I hacking
flex ray no the Ford doesn't have it you
know this is the year of the Ford this
is the year of the Ford last year was
the year of the Toyota the year before
is the year of the Honda
take sure you know it's something we do
casually know this cars running Scheffer
plus see the drive time up there no open
pilot in nissan altima
your the honda should come back any
update on racing today I haven't heard I
haven't heard for the team
I should we should check in we'll go
check in but we'll get an update to you
Skokie's hey oh cute Fleur yes who's the
NiO team there's no meals lag will i
periscope the racing now because I'm
here and I'm coming as social media
coordinator but best have locked a team
, are me in the race today
I'm sure they're gonna kill it she's
gonna get around that track no problem
maybe even kind of fast
we got great steering on the Prius now
we got good acceleration the braking
leaves a little to be desired team come
army yeah we should check out how we're
doing alright scobie's thanks for
joining
that was today's pass go say bye mom all
right vice goes